Alright.
Yes! From home
to the hospital
in under seven minutes.
- We did it.
- Yes.
The hard part is truly over.
No, but come on, we're off
to a great start, aren't we?
I knew I'd get you here fast,
but this has gotta be
some kind of a record.
- Oh, you made it.
- Hi.
- How're you doing?
- How..
How the hell
did you beat us here?
We took a cab.
Did you guys walk?
No.. No, we took a cab too.
But I-I did test runs.
- Hi.
- Hey, you made it.
Okay, is there...some kind
of magic tunnel
to this hospital?
Ross, you stay here and talk.
I'm gonna go have a baby.
Okay, okay.
Um, hi, hi, this is
Rachel Green, I'm Ross Geller.
- We-we called from the car.
- Right.
We have a semiprivate
labor room waiting for you--
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa, I'm sorry, semiprivate?
We-we, uh..
We asked for a private room.
Yes, I see that here.
Unfortunately, we can't
guarantee a private room
and currently,
they're all unavailable.
Man, if only you'd
gotten here sooner.
I'm sorry, semiprivate rooms
are all we have.
Okay, uh,
just give us a second.
Ross?
Yeah?
Give her some money.
I really think
they're out of rooms.
They're not, Ross,
they're just saving them
for the important people, okay?
What-what if I was
the President?
Well, then we'd be
in a lot of trouble.
You don't know
where any countries are.
Okay.
Let's say, would you, um,
would you mind checking again?
See if any, uh, private rooms
may have opened up.
This is a hospital.
Okay, you know what,
I have to say
I don't really care
for your tone
and this is not
the only hospital in the city
and we have no problem to..
Whoa! Oh, gosh, whoa.
- What? What?
- Oh, ow! Contraction.
- Ow, ow.
- Oh.
[groaning]
Would you like to see
a semiprivate room?
Yeah, it couldn't hurt to look.
[theme song]
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's DOA ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been your day ♪
♪ Your week your month
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me too ♪♪
Well, you're only
two centimeters dilated
and we need to get to ten.
- It'll be a while.
- Uh, okay.
I'll be back in an hour
to check you again.
- 'Okay, thank you.'
- 'Thank you.'
Well, I guess we have
some time to kill.
Yeah. Guess so.
- Whew! Check these out.
- Oh!
Never done this before.
Yeah. Well, it looks great.
Thank you very much.
I think we're ready to..
Hi, I'm, uh, I'm Ross.
I'm-I'm here to ruin
this magical day for you.
- Oh, no, no. Not at all.
- Don't worry about it.
Marc Coregar.
This is my wife, Julie.
- Hi, Julie. This is Rachel.
- Hi.
- Oh, hi, Rachel.
- Hi. How are you?
- Is this your first?
- Yeah, it is.
Well, little Jamie here
is our third.
So, if you have any questions
or you need anything
at all, just holler.
- That's so sweet.
- Yeah.
Aww.
Um, say,
I-I opened this earlier
but let me give
you guys some privacy.
No, nonsense,
we're all in this together.
Yeah, we are gonna share
every moment of this with you
and I think
we're gonna have some fun.
- Yeah.
- O-okay, I-I guess.
- Hey, smile.
- Oh, no. I really don't want..
- I-I don't know if we..
- Oh! Thank you.
- Oh, Ross.
- What?
Here comes another contraction.
- Oh.
- Ooh.
- Okay, just breathe.
- Ooh. Whoa!
Oh, oh, honey,
I think I'm having one too.
Oh.
- Oh. Oh.
- Ow. Ow.
Oh..
Oh, hey-hey!
Look at this. Huh? Huh?
- Here we go.
- Oh, no, no! No, no, no!
[instrumental music]
Oh, wow, three hours
and still no baby. Ugh!
The miracle of birth
sure is a snooze fest.
Hey, you wanna see something?
Sure, what?
Okay, um,
this is gonna be fun.
- Watch me freak out Chandler.
- Uh-huh.
- Honey?
- Yeah?
Listen, uh..
...I-I've been
doing some thinking
and I don't know whether
it's because we're here
or...Rachel's giving birth..
...but, um..
I think we should try
to have a baby.
Okay.
Wh-what's that now?
Okay. I've been thinking
about it too
and I-I think we're ready.
Wha..
Are you kidding me?
You-you-you think we're ready
to have a baby now?
Oh, this is fun.
You're ready
to have a baby?
My boy's all grown up.
You said you were ready, too.
Yeah, but I was just
screwing with you
t-to try to get
your voice all high
and weird like mine is now.
Yes, but haven't you wanted
a kid, like, forever?
Okay, just back off, mister.
'Cause I am ready
to have a baby.
I just want Joey to be
the father.
What? Are you crazy?
That's it, right there.
That's all I wanted.
I am so sorry,
the doctor insisted
on closing the curtain
for the exam.
Oh, that's very, really,
very, very okay.
Julie's cervix is dilated
seven centimeters.
That's about four fingers.
Doctor let me feel it myself.
Have you felt
Rachel's cervix, Ross?
- No, I don't know if--
- No, we won't be doing that.
Well, if you like,
you could feel Rachel's
then feel mine to compare.
Am I interrupting?
- Uh, yes. Thank you.
- Oh, no. No.
- Uh, later.
- No, wait..
You can't leave me
alone with these people.
Oh, uh, I'm sorry.
No, Ross. Ross. Ross.
My child has no father.
Hi. Oh. Mwah.
I'm so glad you're here,
but it's gonna be a while.
I wish you'd called first.
Well, that's alright, I'm coming
back later with your father.
Oh, good.
I actually needed to talk
to you before the birth.
Okay. What's up?
I've brought something
that I want to give you..
...assuming, of course,
that you want it.
Ma, you're asking me
to marry you?
This is your grandmother's
engagement ring.
I want you
to give it to Rachel.
Mom, no. Come on.
Thank you.
- Just hear me out.
- No-no, okay?
We've been through this,
we're not gonna get married
just because
she's pregnant, okay?
Honestly, Ross,
this isn't just some girl
you picked up in a bar and..
...humped.
- A child should have a family.
- Ma, you know what?
I-I can't deal
with this right now.
- I'm sorry--
- Just think about it.
If you don't,
I'll talk more about humping.
Give me that.
- Hi, dear.
- Oh, hi.
Oh, thank you
so much for coming.
Ross, get in here.
[instrumental music]
She came and dragged me
out of the labor room
to ask me why
I'm not with Rachel.
Yeah.
Why aren't you with Rachel?
Are you kidding?
Well, look,
we're not gonna be together
just because we're havin'
a baby, okay?
But, you know, it just seems
that you two belong together.
Okay, stop it. I can't deal
with this right now.
- I have to go have a baby.
- Right.
And with who again?
God! He's crazy.
Why doesn't he want
to be with Rachel?
- I know.
- I-I mean, seriously.
She's like the perfect woman.
I mean, I know she turned
me down but if she hadn't
and she wanted to be with me
I would take her
in my arms and..
I haven't bummed you guys out
like this in a while, have I?
- Hey.
- Who's that?
- New people.
What happened
to the Disgustingtons?
They're having their baby.
It's not fair, Ross,
I got here first.
Right after you left, they
wheeled her off into delivery.
Oh, but not before she gave
me a nice juicy shot
of little Jamie
just crownin' away.
Wow. Sorry.
So, uh,
how are the new people?
Well, they have, uh,
some unusual pet names
for each other, including,
um, evil bitch
and, uh, sick bastard.
- Oh, gosh, oh, contraction.
- Yeah?
- Ooh.
- Okay, okay.
- Ow!
- Just breathe.
- Are you looking at her?
- No!
Don't you look at her,
you sick bastard.
Honey, I swear,
I wasn't lookin' at her.
She's in labor.
You like that,
you sick son of a bitch?
Uh, I'm just gonna..
See, see, it's because you were
lookin', you fat pervert.
No, no, I'm-I'm sure
no one was looking.
Just want some privacy.
(evil bitch)
'You miss your girlfriend?'
- Just ignore them, okay?
- Aah.
- Here, you okay?
- Yeah.
- Ross, Ross.
- What? What?
- He's looking at me.
Hey! You want to live
to see your baby?
Don't you talk to my husband
like that, you stupid bastard.
[instrumental music]
Oh, good God!
If you want a baby so bad,
just go steal it.
What is going on with you?
Since when are you so crazy
about babies?
I'm not crazy about babies.
I'm crazy about us.
- What?
- Look..
We've always talked about
having babies someday.
I'm not saying it has
to be right now, but I'm..
...starting to think
that we can handle it.
We're good.
We're really good.
We are pretty good.
But nothing has to happen
till you're ready.
Well, maybe I'm ready now.
I mean, it's a little scary,
but...maybe it's right.
What? It's not right.
We're not ready
to have a kid now.
- What?
- I'm kidding.
This is gonna be fun.
So, we're gonna try?
I mean, we're trying?
We're trying to get pregnant.
Mm..
You know what, I'm not really
comfortable doing this
in front of the babies.
So, when do you wanna
start tryin'?
Alright, hold on a sec.
- Period math?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Well, we could
start trying...now.
Right here?
No, not here.
Maybe here.
Wait a minute, it's perfect,
we've got a lot of time to kill
and we're in a building
that's full of beds.
And it's so clean.
Come on, you stupid machine.
Come on!
Oh, it ate your money?
No.
Alright, I'll see
you downstairs, then.
- Alright.
Hey, I got one!
I got one!
- Hi.
Oh, uh, up or down?
Oh, down, please.
I-I hate to be a ball buster,
but can I just do it?
Yeah.
[clears throat]
- Could you press up, too? Yeah.
- Sure.
I feel so bad for you.
I broke my leg once, too.
Yeah? How'd yours happen?
Well, it's a long story.
It's kind of embarrassing.
Let's just say there was
a typographical error
with a sex manual.
[laughs]
- How about you?
- Car accident.
Oh, let me guess,
some idiot on a cell phone
wasn't paying attention?
Yeah, me.
- Uh, hey, that's me.
- Okay.
Hey, uh, I take it
you're just visiting someone.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
Well, um, if you have some time
you know, and maybe
you might wanna visit
someone else..
- Yeah, I-I would like that.
- Great. I'm in the room..
Wait! What? No!
Elevator! No!
Uh, you-you gotta press
the button.
[instrumental music]
The nurse said they're
bringing in another woman.
[groans]
Is she pregnant yet?
She doesn't need to be.
She'll still have
the baby before I do.
Oh. Oh, Ross,
another contraction.
- Uh, okay. Uh, here, here.
- Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
- That's it, that's it.
- Ooh! Ow! Ow!
Oh, that sounded
like a bad one.
Yeah, it was.
Mine haven't been so bad.
Oh! Here comes one now.
Mmm. Mmh!
Whoa. That was a big one. Ugh!
Excuse me. Could you help me
with something?
The patient I'm looking
for has a broken leg
and he's in a wheelchair
and, um, he's like
early to mid-30s,
very attractive.
I think I know
who you're talkin' about.
Oh, yay! Great. Okay,
what room number is he in?
I'm sorry, that information
is restricted to hospital staff.
Uh, she's with me
Dr. Drake Ramoray.
Dr. Drake who?
Ramoray. It's Portuguese.
We need that information.
I'm a doctor.
- A doctor at this hosp--
- Damn it, woman!
We're losing precious time.
Now, do you want
this man's blood on your head?
- Hands.
- Hands?
It is absolutely essential that
you tell me what room the man
my assistant described
is staying in.
He's a patient of mine. I've
been treating him for years.
- He's in room 816.
- 816. Thank you.
Thank you.
- And what is his name?
- No!
[instrumental music]
- I think we found a place.
- Okay.
[both moaning]
Wait. Don't we want
to set the mood a little?
Oh, okay, uh..
We'll dim the lights,
dim the lights.
(Monica)
'Okay.'
Or turn them out altogether.
Uh, no scented candles.
Okay, here.
There we go.
Uh, okay, okay.
Make me sterile, but okay.
Okay. That's right.
Oh, wait.
Do we have a condom?
Oh, right.
[door opens]
Yes, 98.6.
You're gonna be fine.
Ooh, this is it.
[gasps]
That's him, that's him.
Great. Well, go get him.
Wait a second.
Or maybe
you could go in first.
Yeah, he's not really my type.
No, not you.
Dr. Drake Ramoray.
You could ask him questions
and see what he's like.
People tell doctors
everything.
But you said he was
this great guy.
But lately all the guys
I meet seem really nice at first
and then they turn out to be
the biggest jerks.
- You do attract some stinkers.
- Yeah, I know.
Dr. Long, I've been at this
for 17 hours.
Three women have come
and gone with their babies.
You got to give me
some good news.
How many centimeters
am I dilated, eight?
- Nine?
- Three.
Just three?
I'm dilated three.
We are moving along,
just slowly.
Don't worry,
you're doing great.
I'll be back soon.
Thank you.
Hey, you know what?
I'm not waiting.
I'm gonna push this baby out.
I'm doing it. I mean, it's what,
three centimeters?
That's gotta be
like this, right?
Actually, it's,
it's more like this.
Ah, stupid metric system.
[woman screaming]
Oh, my. We're gonna
need to take you
straight to the delivery room.
Oh, for the love of God!
Hi, I'm Dr. Drake Ramoray.
I have a few routine questions
I need to ask you.
Really? I've been dealing
with Dr. Wells.
I know, but I'm a neurologist,
and just to be on the safe side
Dr. Wells wanted a more
comprehensive overview
of your status,
so...he sent me.
Dr. Wells is a woman.
That was a test.
Good response.
[clears throat]
Alright, uh, full name?
Clifford Burnett.
Date of birth?
November 16th, 1968.
Age?
Can't you figure that out
based on my date of birth?
I'm a doctor, Cliff,
not a mathematician.
- I'm 33.
- Okay.
- And, uh, are you married?
- No.
Oh, really? So, 33 and single.
Would you say
you have commitment issues?
Are all the questions
this personal?
Yes.
Well, uh, if you must know,
I'm a widower.
Oh, that's terrible.
I'm-I'm really sorry.
- Yeah.
- Mm.
Do you sleep with women
and never call them again?
- No.
- Excellent. Excellent.
And, uh, finally,
are you into any weird stuff
you know, sexually?
[scoffs]
Wha.. No.
Ooh, wrong answer.
[instrumental music]
- What else? What else?
- Uh, well, he's 33.
- Um, uh-huh.
- A widower.
- Oh.
- He seemed like a stand-up guy.
Oh, and he's not into
anything weird, sexually.
Enter Pheebs.
- This room's available.
- Okay, okay.
Wait, you listen to me,
you listen to me.
Since I have been waiting,
four women, that's four
one higher than the number of
centimeters that I am dilated
have come and gone
with their babies!
I'm next. It's my turn!
It's only fair!
And if you bring in one
more woman and she has
her baby before me,
I'm going to sue you.
Not this hospital,
I'm gonna sue you.
And my husband,
he is a lawyer.
Uh, Rach.
You get back
on that case, honey!
I don't think the next patient
is very far along.
Okay, well, then, bring her in.
Oh...my..
...God!
[instrumental music]
I...can't...believe this.
And yet somehow it's true.
I mean, this is so great.
We're gonna be baby buddies.
[grating laugh]
Squeeze your legs together
and cover the baby's ears.
- Hey, sweetie.
- Hi. Hi, sweetheart.
This is my husband Sid.
I don't think you've met him.
- Ross, Rachel, this is Sid.
- Hi.
I nabbed him a year ago
at the dermatologist's office.
Thank God for adult acne, huh?
[grating laugh]
I still can't believe it.
I'm the luckiest guy
in the world.
Really?
- What'd he say?
- You know what?
You have to speak very loudly
when you're talking to Sid
'cause he's almost
completely deaf.
- Oh, of course, he is.
- Oh, there you go.
So, congratulations, you two.
I didn't even
know you got married.
- Oh, we didn't.
- No, no, we..
- What?
- Oh, uh..
We're-we're just
having this baby together
but, uh, uh,
that's all, you know?
Why?
Uh, well, um..
...we're just not
in that place, you know
but we're very excited
about this.
Oh. Well, then shut me up.
Just tell me how.
Uh-oh. Oh, I feel another
one coming.
[groaning]
[theme music]